Yuki-chan, it's been a while.
ゆきちゃん、久しぶりです
It's been a while.
久 しぶりです
Is it cold?
寒いの?
It's cold.
寒いです
It's cold today.
寒いね、今日ね
It's really cold.
めちゃくちゃ寒いね
It was nice to meet you after a long time.
久々に会えてさ、よかったけどさ、
Why didn't you contact me back?
なんで連絡返しとかなかったの?
I'm angry.
怒ってて
Who?
誰が?
Yuki-chan?
ゆきちゃんが?
I.
私が
Why are you angry?
なんで怒ってんの?
It was splashed on my face a little bit.
ちょっと顔にかけられたの
I'm a little angry.
少し怒ってて
It was splashed on my face.
顔にかけられたの
Are you mad because you got it splashed on your face last time?
前回顔にかけられたから怒ってんの?
It's cute though.
可愛いんだけど
Seriously.
まじで
Sorry, sorry.
ご めんごめん
Sorry for making you laugh.
笑っちゃってごめん
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Are you really angry about that?
それでガチで怒ってんの?
I'm angry.
怒ってます
Was it a shock to have it thrown on your face?
顔にかけられたのショックだった?
I'm angry.
怒ってます
I'm angry all the time.
ずっと怒ってます
That's right, sorry.
そうだ、ごめん
Well, well, well.
まあまあまあ
I'm sorry.
ごめんだけどさ
But you have to pay back the elementary school money.
だけど、小学金返さないといけないでしょ
Right?
でしょ?
You said it wasn't the semester yet.
学期になってないとって言ってたでしょ
You said you wouldn't have to pay back the elementary school money.
小学金返さないとって言ってたでしょ
That's why, uncle, I'll cooperate with you again.
だから、おじさんまた協力するから
Go to someone you know.
仲のある人に行こうよ
I'll try not to do gunners today.
今日はガンサーしないようにする
Please don't do that.
しないようにね
Don't do it.
しないように
Please do not do this.
しないようにお願いします
Are you hungry?
お腹減った?
a little bit.
ちょっと
Just walk on the wall.
ちょっとさ、壁歩きしてさ
What is that?
って何?
It was a fortune.
おみくじだったりさ
Come and visit us.
お参りとかしてさ
That's what I was thinking.
って思ってんだけど
Have you been to Ryumori?
竜森行った?
Just right.
ちょうどいいね
So, do you want to come here?
じゃあ、ここに来る?
please.
お願いします
Well then, let's get along today.
じゃあ、今日は仲良くしようよ
Riku-chan, did the baby come?
りくちゃん、おさんしゅくだんご来た?
Osanshukudango.
おさんしゅくだんご
amazing.
すごい
Does this have any flavor?
これさ、味あんの?
please.
どうぞ
Thank you very much.
どうぞございます
first time?
初めて?
first time.
初めて
please.
どうぞ
Has the rain gotten heavier?
雨強くなった?
What is pink?
ピンクは何?
Cherry blossom flavor?
桜の味?
Yeah.
うん
Really?
本当に?
Yeah, probably.
うん、多分
Really?
本当 に?
本当に?
Well, there are various flavors.
じゃあ、いろいろ味あんだ
Yeah.
うん
delicious?
おいしい?
Well then, let's do this next.
じゃあ、次にこうか
hey.
ね
Was it delicious?
おいしかった?
It was delicious.
おいしかったです
Really?
本当に?
Really.
本当に
Good for you.
よかったね
Well then, Yuki-chan, yes.
じゃあ、ゆきちゃん、はい
Omikuji.
おみくじ
Yes, it's Anko.
はい、あんこでーす
What number did it come out?
何番出た?
What number is it?
何 番なの?
Which is 43?
43ってどれ?
Are you shooting from the top?
それ一番上から撮るの?
Is that what it is?
そういうもんなの?
Isn't that what it is?
それもんじゃないの?
Take two pictures over there.
あっち2枚撮ってみて
That's great.
よくばりだな
copper?
どう?
Did you write anything good?
いいこと書いてあった?
Come here.
こっち来てね
copper?
どう?
Did you write anything good?
いいこと書いてあった?
Eh, hmm.
え、うーん
Oh, I don't know.
え、わかんない
Haven't you written it?
書いてないの?
I don't even know what kind of kitsch this is.
これ何キッチなのかもわかんない
Not written?
書いてない?
Eh, what kind of kitsch is that?
え、何キッチなの?
this.
これ
Oh, it's kitsch.
あ、キッチだ
Kitch.
キッチ
Kitch?
キッチ?
This is kitsch.
これ、 キッチ
Kitch?
キッチ?
It says kitsch.
キッチって書いてある
That's good, isn't it?
よかったでしょ
Oh, good.
え、よかった
Do you like the big kitchen?
大キッチがいい?
大キッチがいいの?
Doesn't it say that there is a possibility that you will be separated from important tasks?
大事な仕事を分かれる可能性がありますって書いてない?
No, no, no.
ないないない
Oh, lie?
あ、嘘?
No, no, no.
ないないない
Oh, isn't there such a thing?
あ、そういうのはないの?
Yeah.
うん
Really?
ほ っか
Well then, let's go do it.
じゃあ、そこ、やりに行こう
Let's tie this.
これ結ぼう
Shall we tie it?
結ぼう?
Yeah.
うん
Drinking today, oh no.
今日飲み、あ、違って
That's when you take it home or go home.
それがお持ち帰り、帰りの際だから
Not so.
そうじゃない
Yeah.
うん
It's okay because it's not.
そうじゃないから大丈夫だよね
I was told I could take it home with me.
持ち帰っていいんだって
Yeah.
うん
Well, I'll just show it to my boyfriend.
じゃあ、ただ彼氏に見せてあげる
What's the point of showing it?
見せて何になるの?
this.
これ
Well then, let's visit for the last time.
じゃあ、次は最後お参りしよう
Yeah.
うん
Come on, let's go to the hotel.
ほんで、ホテル行こう
good?
いい?
Okay.
いいよ
Yuki-chan.
ゆきちゃん
Yuki-chan, take a picture.
ゆきちゃん、撮れ
Teacher 17.
先生17ね
It's a powerful role.
圧役だよ
terrible.
やばい
What should I do?
どうしよう
picture?
え?
Do you want to visit?
お参りする?
It will be after you visit.
お参りしたらなりますね
I don't know.
わかんない
Will it heal?
治るかな?
picture?
え?
This, pressure, let's make pressure bad.
これ、圧役、圧役を悪いにしよう
I don't know.
わかんない
Oh, I don't know.
え、わかんない
Yeah.
うん
But the translation is different.
でも翻訳が違う
Uncle: You're not interested at all.
おっ ちゃん さ、全く興味ないんだよね
of voice.
声の
Wow!
うわ ー!
It hurts.
痛え
So what does it feel like?
だから何って感じなんだよね
It looked great.
めっちゃ見えた
Let's be careful.
気をつけよう
I mean, whether it's a powerful role or a translation.
だってさ、圧役だろうが翻訳だろうだったら
Yeah.
うん
Hey, ah.
ね、あー
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
Ah, that's it.
あー、それよ
Oh, by the way, who is your boyfriend?
え、ちなみに彼氏は?
What role is it?
何役なの?
translation.
翻訳
Huh, 1981?
え、昭和58年?
different.
違う
2000?
平成12年?
Yes, in 2000.
うん、平成12年
The rest is his translation.
あとは、彼ちゃん、翻訳なんだ
Well then, come and visit us.
じゃあ、お参りして
Please pray.
お参りして
Just a moment, okay?
ちょっと、ね
Celebrate a little.
ちょっとお祝い込んで
Great job.
すごいやった
Can I throw you a book? From here.
本投げていいかな、ここから
Okay.
いいよ
Well, let's throw it.
じゃあ、投げよう
Did you throw it?
投げた?
I threw it.
投げた
You threw it.
投げれたね
I threw it.
投げた
It was so crowded, so full, I almost got an allergy.
人混みさ、いっぱいでさ、ちょっとアレルギー出そうになった
What are you talking about? You look like this guy.
何言ってんだ、こいつみたいな
Yeah.
うん
Well, what did you ask for?
え、何にお願いした?
What did you ask for?
何にお願いした?
Go healthy.
健康に行く
Healthy?
健康に?
healthy?
健康?
healthy.
健康
If you think about health, why not come?
健康に考えるとしたら、来ないの?
Yes, but it's healthy.
ええ、でも一応、健康
Really?
本当に?
I hope that only he will be able to separate from his ulterior motives soon.
裏心の中で、早く彼しか分かれますように
No, stop it.
いや、やめて
Isn't that what it is?
そういうのじゃない?
That's right, that's what it is.
そうなんだね、そういうの
Well, I was able to make a pilgrim.
ちゃんとだけどね、お参りちゃんの出来たの
Please say that's the end of your first visit.
初詣じゃあ、それで終わりでって言ってください
good?
いい?
It's over.
終了です
Well, today, let's go to the hotel again.
じゃあ、今日はさ、ちょっとまたホテル行って、
I'm doing a lot of things.
いろいろさ、やっているからさ
Yeah.
うん
good?
いい?
It's over.
終わりです
nice.
いい ね
Let's go with Lampe.
ランペで行こう
yes.
はい
Yuki-chan.
ゆきちゃん
good morning.
おはよう
おはようございます
Were you sleeping?
寝てたの?
I'm not sleeping.
寝てないです
Did you think about it?
考え事したの?
It's something to think about.
考え事です
what happened?
どうしたの?
I guess I was nervous after coming to the hotel.
ホテル来て緊張しちゃったのかと
That makes me nervous.
それ、緊張します
Still nervous?
まだ緊張する?
I'm still nervous.
まだ緊張します
まだ緊張するね
That's right.
そりゃそうだよね
そりゃそうだね
How is the hotel today?
今日のホテルはどうですか?
beautiful.
綺麗
beautiful?
綺麗?
beautiful.
綺麗
Yuki-chan said let's go.
ゆきちゃんって行こうって言うのはさ、
As much as possible, I mean a clean hotel.
なるべくさ、綺麗なホテルっていうのはさ、
That's what I'm thinking.
思ってるんだけどさ
Did you like this hotel?
このホテル気に入ってくれました?
It was so beautiful.
すごく綺麗だった
Really?
本当に?
Why are you talking about PE like that?
なんでそんな体育ざわりしてるの?
why?
なんで?
Naturally.
自然に
I think it would be better if it didn't have a physical education feel to it.
体育ざわりじゃない方がいいかしら
Oh, would you mind a little more?
あ、もうちょいいいすか?
Yeah?
うん?
Ah, nice, nice.
あ、いいっすねいいっすね
I'm not sleeping.
寝てないよ
That's good.
いいっすね
No, that little panty line.
いや、そのちょっとパンチララインをね
Oh, no.
あー、やだ
No way.
やだな
That's amazing.
すごいやだ
すごいやだな
It's embarrassing because I did it unconsciously.
無意識やってたから、恥ずかしい
lie?
う そ?
Yeah.
うん
It's erotic, today too.
エロいね、今日もね
Isn't it erotic?
エロくない?
It's not erotic.
エロくないです
Are you nervous?
緊張すんの?
I'm nervous.
緊張しますって
lie?
うそ?
So, shall we go eat again?
じゃ、またご飯食べに行く?
from now.
今から
picture?
え?
No way.
やだ
Right?
でしょ?
No way.
やだ
It's okay to eat something like this.
食べるのはさ、もういいじゃん、こんなもんで
Yeah.
うん
That's why, as I said at the beginning,
だからさ、冒頭でもさ、言ったけどさ、
Today is just a matter of making up.
今日はちょっと、ね、仲直りということでさ
Let's make up.
仲直りしようよ
good?
いい?
Will you make up?
仲直りしてくれる?
yes.
はい
cute.
かわいい
what happened?
どうしたの?
Does it remain warped?
反り残し?
Oh, no.
え、違う
what happened?
どうしたの?
My legs followed me.
後がついちゃったよ、足に
why?
なんで?
Does it hurt?
痛いの?
Yeah, I was curious.
うん、気になっちゃった
Is that so?
そうなの?
Well, that means you liked the hotel today too.
じゃあ、今日のホテルも気に入ってくれたっていうことだから
Yeah.
うん
hey.
ね
Last time, what was that?
前回さ、ちょっとさ、その、何?
Show it on your face?
顔に出して?
Yeah.
うん
Are you angry?
怒ったんでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Sorry, that's it.
ごめんね、だからそれは
So what?
で、何?
Did your eyes hurt?
目、目が痛かったの?
My eyes turned a little red.
目がちょっと赤くなっちゃった
Did you turn red?
赤くなっちゃったの?
Your eyes are sensitive.
敏感だね、目がね
Yeah.
うん
I see.
そっか
So, should I be grateful if you don't let me see it?
じゃあ、目にかけないようにだったら感謝いいのかな?
Not good, not good.
よくない、よくない
That's not what it means.
そういうことじゃない
Well then, I won't be grateful today.
じゃあ、今日は感謝なしということでね
But, I'm sorry, but I just can't resist.
だけど、ごめんだけど、ちょっと我慢できなくて、
I'm sorry if I went to your face.
その、お顔の方に行っちゃったらごめんね
You might not listen to what I say.
言うこと聞かないかもしれない
Yeah, I feel like that.
うん、って感じ
Yeah, that's what it feels like.
うん、 って 感じ
Yeah, I see.
うん、そっか
Yeah.
うん
I see.
なるほどね
Well, today, just a little bit.
まあ、だけど今日はさ、ちょっとね、
It's been a while since we met, and we're making up.
久々に会ってさ、仲直りっていうことだからさ、
Get along well.
仲良くして
I'm really sorry, but...
ほんとごめんね、だけど
It was an accident.
事故だった
Enough is enough, right?
もういいでしょ?
Have you really conveyed your feelings?
もう いっぱい、精意伝わった?
The spirit of saying sorry.
ごめんねの精意
Did you get it a little bit?
ちょっと伝わった?
Oh, really?
あ、本当に?
Well, all that's left is how to convey your intentions.
じゃあまあ、あとはさ、精意の伝え方